{
    "subject": "Erica_Kane",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jackson_Montgomery",
    "human_readable": "Erica Kane is married to Jackson Montgomery.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884571433067322,
            "question": "Is Jackson Montgomery married to Erica Kane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.979042649269104,
            "question": "Is there a marital relationship between Erica Kane and Jackson Montgomery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8905669450759888,
            "question": "Who is Erica Kane married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7681777477264404,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Erica Kane."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567230463027954,
            "question": "To whom is Erica Kane currently wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7331379652023315,
            "question": "Who is Jackson Montgomery's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6168396472930908,
            "question": "What is the name of Erica Kane's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42871975898742676,
            "question": "What is the name of Erica Kane's partner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40725767612457275,
            "question": "Who shares a marital bond with Erica Kane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34103715419769287,
            "question": "With whom did Erica Kane tie the knot?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Erica Kane is married to Jackson Montgomery.",
            "html": "yago_29589_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital bond with Erica Kane?",
            "html": "yago_29589_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Erica Kane's partner?",
            "html": "yago_29589_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Erica Kane's husband?",
            "html": "yago_29589_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29589_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently mention that Erica Kane is married to Jackson Montgomery, and even provide details about their relationship and interactions with each other. This supports the triple that Erica Kane is indeed married to Jackson Montgomery."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information across the documents consistently indicates that Erica Kane is married to Jackson Montgomery. This is supported by multiple references in the texts provided, such as the description of their marriage on May 29, 2005, and the mention of Erica's marital status including her husband being Jackson Montgomery."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}